Guide to the Picture File, 1600s-1979 and undated, bulk 1814-1950
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
- People Series, 1700s, 1714-1974, 1900s and undated, (22 boxes)
  - Nel--Z, 1749-1968, 1900s and undated
    - Terry, Dame Ellen, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1644)
    - Thackeray, William Makepeace, 1911, (engraving) (Box 34, Folder M1645)
      From Harper's Monthly Magazine, June 1911.
    - Theodosia, 1802, (engraving) (Folder M1646)
    - Thomas, Edward L., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1647)
    - Thomas, George Henry, 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1648)
    - Thomas, James Augustus, 1900s, (4 black-and-white photographs and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1649)
    - Thomas, William Holland, 1800s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1650)
      "Images may not be reproduced without permission of portrait owner."
      These photographs of a portrait are duplicates.
      Includes biographical and historical information.
      Two negatives removed to N27 in the Negatives Series.
    - Thomas, William Holland, 1858 and 1800s, (2 negatives)
      Removed from M1650 to the Negatives Series.
    - Thompson, Edgar, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1651)
    - Thompson, John Reuben, 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1652)
    - Thompson, Merriwether Jeff, 1800s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1653)
    - Thornton, Henry T., 1929 Mar., (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1654)
    - Tilghman, William, 1827, (engraving) (Folder M1655)
    - Tillman, Benjamin Ryan, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration, stereograph) (Folder M1656)
      Transferred from the William Watts Ball Mss.
      Stereograph removed to S38 in the Stereographs Series.
    - Tillotson, John, undated, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV160, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
    - Timrod, Henry, undated, (black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1657)
    - Timrod, Henry and William Henry, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1658)
    - Titus Livius, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1659)
    - Todd, Thomas, 1889, (engraving) (Folder M1660)
    - Tomline, Sir George Pretyman, undated, (engraving)
    - Tomo Chachi Mico, undated, (lithograph) (Folder M1661)
    - Tompkins, Christopher, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1662)
    - Tompkins, Daniel D., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1663)
    - Toms, Clinton W., 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1664)
    - Tooke, John Horne, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1665)
      Original newsprint biographical note photocopied.
    - Toombs, Robert, 1800s, (4 engravings) (Folder M1666)
    - Torrens, Sir Henry, 1829, (engraving) (Folder M1667)
      Includes possibly authentic signature of Henry Torrens.
    - Torsch, John W., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1668)
    - Townshend, Lady, 1806 June 1, (engraving) (Folder M1669)
    - Tracy, Benjamin Franklin, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1670)
    - Tracy, Edward Dott, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1671)
    - Trimble, Isaac Ridgeway, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1672)
    - Trimble, Robert, 1889, (engraving) (Folder M1673)
    - Troup, George Michael, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1674)
    - True, Herbert H., 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1675)
    - Tucker, Jane Skelton (Ellis) and Tucker, (Nathaniel) Beverly, 1901 Oct. 15 and undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1676)
      The smaller photograph is from the C. C. Clay Mss., the larger from the Munford-Ellis Papers.
    - Turner, Jesse, Sr., 1800s, (1 card photograph and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1677)
      One engraving removed to Folder OV162, Box LG04 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Turner, Rebecca J. (Allen), 1855 and undated, (1 black-and-white photograph and 1 card photograph) (Folder M1678)
      The black-and-white photograph was copied from a daguerrotype.
    - Twiggs, David E., 1800s, (1 black-and-white illustration and 1 engraving) (Folder M1679)
    - Tyler, John, 1863 and 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1680)
    - Umberto I, King of Italy, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1681)
    - Underwood, Washington Quincy, undated, (card photograph)
      Removed to Folder OV163, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
      One negative removed to N28 in the Negatives Series.
    - Union Commanders: Farragut, Meade..., 1884, (black-and-white photographic illustration)
      Removed to Folder OV164, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
    - Union Naval Commanders, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1682)
    - Untermeyer, Samuel, 1900s, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1683)
    - Updike, John Hoyer, 1900s, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1684)
      Gift of Professor Clarence Gohdes.
    - Valentine, Edward V., 1900s, (card photograph) (Folder M1685)
      Transferred from the Albert Aylor Papers.
    - Van Buren, Martin, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1686)
    - Van Dorn, Earl, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1687)
      From the C. C. Clay Papers.
    - Van Etten, Solomon, 1864 Apr. 12, (card photograph) (Folder M1688)
      Solomon Van Etten, 56th N.Y. Inf. (Tenth Legion).
    - Van Noppen, Charles Leonard, undated, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV165, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
      From the Charles L. Van Noppen Mss. Includes signature of Charles Van Noppen.
    - Van Noppen, Leonard Charles, undated, (1 engraving, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration and 1 card photograph) (Folder M1689)
      The engraving and illustration are both from the Charles L. Van Noppen Mss.
    - Vance, Zebulon Baird, 1876, (card photograph) (Folder M1690)
    - Vance, Zebulon Baird, et al., 1897 Oct. 20, (card photograph) (Folder M1691)
    - Vance, Zebulon Baird and Vance, Harriet N. (Espy), 1800s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1692)
    - Vanderbilt University -- Medical Students, 1885-1886, (card photograph) (Folder M1693)
    - Vanderbilt, William Henry, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1694)
      Transferred from the C. C. Jones, Jr. Scrapbook.
    - Vansittart, Nicholas, First Baron Bexley, 1831, (engraving) (Folder M1695)
    - Vassali, Count, 1820 Nov. 10, (engraving) (Folder M1696)
    - Vauban, Sebastian le Prestre, Marquis de, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1697)
    - Victoria, Queen of Great Britain, undated, (color illustration) (Folder M1698)
    - Villiers, George, First Duke of Buckingham (1592-1628), 1825 Sept. 1, (engraving)
      Removed to Folder OV166, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
    - da Vinci, Leonardo, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1699)
    - de Voltaire, Francois Marie Arouet, undated, (postcard) (Folder M1700)
    - Von Schwartze, Charles H., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1701)
    - Voorhees, Daniel Wolsey, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1702)
    - Wagoner, Charles Boyd, 1913 Sept., 1922, 1800s and undated, (5 card photographs) (Folder M1703)
    - Waite, Morrison Remick, 1800s, (engraving) (Box 35, Folder M1704)
    - Walker, Gilbert Carlton, 1871 June 3, (card photograph) (Folder M1705)
    - Walker, H. T., circa 1860s, (card photograph) (Folder M1706)
    - Walker, Norman, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1707)
    - Walker, Ralph, 1803 Dec. 1, (engraving) (Folder M1708)
    - Wallace, Henry Agard, 1900s, (clipping) (Folder M1709)
    - Wallace, W. H., undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1710)
      Includes W. H. Wallace's signature.
      One card photograph was removed to Folder OV167, Box LG04, in the Oversize Subseries. Depicts Wallace and other members of the S.C. legislature of 1876.
    - Walpole, Robert, Earl of Oxford, 1836 Dec. 1 and 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1711)
      One engraving removed to Folder OV168, Box LG04 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Walsingham, Sir Francis (1530?-1590), 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1712)
      One engraving removed to OV169, Box LG04 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Walton, George, undated, (4 engravings and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1713)
      One of these engravings is from the Georgia Historical Society, and another engraving is from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
    - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1928 and 1900s, (9 black-and-white photographs and 4 postcards) (Folder M1714.1)
    - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1900s, (7 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1714.2)
    - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1935 July and 1900s, (5 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1714.3)
    - Warburton, Amber Arthur, 1898-1976, 1920 June 21-1922 Sept. 1, (3 diplomas (Folder M1714.4)
      Three negatives removed to N29 in the Negatives Series.
      Two black-and-white photographs and one broadside removed to OV170.1-2, Box LG04 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Warner, Hiram, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1715)
    - Warren, Joseph, 1835, (engraving) (Folder M1716)
    - Warrington, Lewis, 1815 Oct. 2, (engraving) (Folder M1717)
      "See picture of the 'Peacock,' whick Lewis Warrington commanded during the War of 1812."
    - Washington, Andrew Coyle, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1718)
    - Washington, Bushrod, 1891, (engraving) (Folder M1719)
    - Washington, George, 1800s and 1836, (5 engravings and 1 color illustration) (Folder M1720.1)
      One engraving is from John Marshall's "The Life of George Washington...," Vol. 1, 2nd ed., Philadelphia, James Crissy, 1836.
      One engraving is from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
      See also M1794 for an additional engraving and ALN.
    - Washington, George, 1800s, 1833-1834 and 1900s, (5 engravings and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1720.2)
      Two engravings are from Jared Spark's "The Writings of George Washington...," Vol. 3, 1834 and 1847. One engraving is from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress. The photograph is from the Socialist Party Records.
    - Washington, George, 1800s, 1796-1893, (4 engravings and 1 color illustration) (Folder M1720.3)
      Two engravings are from Jared Spark's "The Writings of George Washington...," Vol. 2, 1834. One engraving is from "Sons of the American Revolution," New York, Year Book, 1893.
    - Washington, William, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1721)
    - Watson, R., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1722)
      Transferred from the Eugene Marshall Hendrix Mss.
    - Watson, Sereno, undated, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1723)
    - Watts, George Washington, 1900s, (1 clipping and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1724)
      The photograph has a negative available.
    - Watts, Richard Cannon, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1725)
      Transferred from the William Watts Ball Papers.
    - Watts-Dunton, Walter Theodore, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1726)
    - Wayne, Anthony, 1858, 1863, 1796 and 1800s, (6 engravings) (Folder M1727)
      One engraving is from Vol. 2 of "History of the United States of America" by Henry William Elion, published in N.Y. in 1905.
      Two engravings are from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
    - Wayne, James M., 1890, (2 engravings) (Folder M1728)
    - Webster, Daniel, 1800s and circa 1868, (5 engravings) (Folder M1729)
      One engraving is from Alexander H. Stephens' "A Constitutional View of the War Between the States...," Vol. 1.
    - Wedderburn, Alexander, First Earl of Rosslyn, 1796 July 1, (engraving) (Folder M1730)
    - Weedon, Miss Howard, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1731)
    - Weeks, Stephen Beauregard, 1900s, (2 card photographs) (Folder M1732)
    - Welch, William Henry, undated, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1733)
    - Welles, Gideon, 1865, (engraving) (Folder M1734)
    - Wesley, Charles (1707-1788), 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1735)
    - Wesley, John, 1790, 1775 Jan. 20 and 1800s, (4 engravings and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1736)
      All of these items have negatives available.
      The first two engravings were loaned by Mrs. Marmaduke Floyd. The original folder included several pages of biographical information on John Wesley; these were replaced by photocopies.
    - Wesley, Samuel, 1836, 1800s and undated, (3 engravings) (Folder M1737)
      The last engraving is a gift from Frank C. Brown.
    - West, Benjamin, 1820-1823 Jan. 1 and 1800s, (5 engravings) (Folder M1738)
    - Wheat, Leo, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1739)
    - Wheeler, Joseph, 1800s, (2 engravings, 1 black-and-white photographic illustration and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Box 36, Folder M1740)
    - White, Hugh Lawson, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1741)
    - Whitefield, George, 1834, 1749 and undated, (5 lithographs and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1742.1)
      Four of these lithographs have negatives available.
      Three lithographs were taken from "Memories of Rev. George Whitefield" by John Gillies, New Haven, Whitemore, Buckingham and H. Mansfield, 1834.
    - Whitefield, George, 1834 and undated, (4 lithographs (Folder M1742.2)
      Three of these lithographs have negatives available.
      One lithograph was taken from "Memories of Rev. George Whitefield" by John Gillies. New Haven. Whitemore, Buckingham and H. Mansfield, 1834. Two lithographs were taken from Jones: Biographical Sketches of the Delegates from Georgia to the Continental Congress.
    - Whitehead, George, undated, (black-and-white illustration)
      Removed to Folder OV171, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
    - Whitehouse, Albert, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1743)
    - Whittemore, B. F., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1744)
    - Whittier, John Greenleaf, undated, (1 handbill and 1 black-and-white illustration) (Folder M1745)
    - Wilberforce, William, 1814 Nov. 1, 1798 Apr. 28 and 1800s, (5 engravings) (Folder M1746)
    - Wilde, Oscar Fingal O'Flahertie Wills, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1747)
    - Wilde, Richard Henry, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1748)
    - Wiley, Isaac William, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1749)
    - Wiley, Louis, 1913 Feb. 7, (card photograph)
      Removed to Folder OV172, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
    - Wilhelm I (Friedrich), King of Prussia (1688-1740), 1877, (card photograph) (Folder M1750)
    - Wilkes, Charles, 1864, (engraving) (Folder M1751)
    - Wilks, Robert, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1752)
    - Willard, A. J., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1753)
      Contains possibly authentic signature of A. J. Willard.
    - Willard, W. H., 1900s, (card photograph)
      Removed to Folder OV173, Box LG04, Oversize Subseries.
    - William III, King of Great Britain, undated, (3 engravings) (Folder M1754)
      One engraving removed to Folder OV174, Box LG04 in the Oversize Subseries.
    - Williams, Thomas, undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1755)
      Transferred from the George Smith Houston Papers.
    - Willis, Robert H., undated, (card photograph) (Folder M1756)
      Transferred from the 9019 Papers.
    - Wilkie, Wendell Lewis, 1900s, (clipping) (Folder M1757)
    - Wilson, Daniel (1778-1858), 1833, (engraving) (Folder M1758)
    - Wilson, Henry, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1759)
      Includes possibly authentic signature of Henry Wilson.
    - Wilson, Woodrow, 1913, May 1914 and 1900s, (2 black-and-white illustrations and 1 black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1760)
      The first illustration is from "The Journal of the American Historical Society," Vol. XII. New York, 1913.
    - Winter, Cornelius, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1761)
    - Winterhalter, A. G., Admiral, U. S. N., 1916 Jan. 10, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1762)
    - Wirt, William, 1863 and 1800s, (3 engravings) (Folder M1763)
    - Wise, Henry Alexander, 1800s, (2 engravings) (Folder M1764)
    - Witherspoon, John, undated, (engraving) (Folder M1765)
    - Wolf, Frederick Adolphus, circa 1938, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1766)
    - Wolfe, Thomas Clayton, undated, (handbill) (Folder M1767)
    - Wolfe, Thomas Clayton, 1937, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1768)
      From the Hubert H. Hayes Papers. Signed by Mabel (Wolfe) Wheaton.
    - Wolfe, Thomas Clayton, and Julia Elizabeth (Westall) Wolfe, 1937, (black-and-white photograph) (Folder M1769)
    - Wolsey, Thomas, et al., undated, (engraving) (Folder M1770)
    - Woods, W. B., 1890, (engraving) (Folder M1771)
    - Wool, John Ellis, 1859, (engraving) (Folder M1772)
      Contains possibly authentic signature of John Ellis Wool.
    - Woolner, Thomas, 1861 and 1800s, (2 black-and-white illustrations) (Folder M1773)
    - Woolsey, Theodore D., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1774)
    - Worth, Jonathan, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1775)
    - Worth, William Jenkins, 1848, (engraving) (Folder M1776)
    - Wrangham, Francis (1769-1842), 1838, (engraving) (Folder M1777)
    - Wright, G. W., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1778)
    - Wright, Marcus J., 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1779)
    - Wright, Richard Harvey, 1800s, (2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1780)
    - Wright, Richard Harvey, undated, (black-and-white photographic illustration) (Folder M1781)
      Copy of a photograph from the American Historical Society. Includes possibly authentic signature of Richard Harvey Wright.
    - Wriothesley, Henry, Third Earl of Southhampton (1563-1624), 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1782)
      One of William Shakespeare's patrons.
    - Wylie, Walker Gill, circa 1884, (card photograph) (Folder M1783)
    - Wythe, George, 1800s, (engraving) (Folder M1784)
    - Yancey, William Lowndes, 1800s, (lithograph) (Folder M1785)
    - Yarbrough, Richard and Tabitha (Johns), 1800s, (2 card photographs and 2 black-and-white photographs) (Folder M1786)
      One negative removed to N30 in the Negatives Series.
    - Young, Pierce Manning Butler, 1800s, (1 black-and-white photographic illustration and 1 engraving) (Folder M1787)
      The illustration is from Charles E. Jones' Scrapbook.
    - Zacharias, Peter, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1788)
    - Zollicoffer, Felix Kirk, 1800s, (card photograph) (Folder M1789)
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon, 1700s, (color engraving) (Folder M1790)
      Enclosed in frame which also includes mounted, undated, signed missive written by Bonaparte to the "ministre de la guerre." Location: locked Carrell 215.
    - Franklin, Benjamin, 1706 and undated, (3 color engravings) (Folder M1791)
      One engraving is French, dated 1706. Enclosed in frame which also includes mounted, signed receipt dated 1757 written by Franklin. Location: locked Carrell 215.
    - Hamilton, Alexander, 1700s, (color engraving) (Folder M1792)
      Included with signed letter written by Hamilton, signed by George Washington twice and sealed with his signet ring, and sent to Thomas Jefferson. Location: locked Carrell 215.
    - Jefferson, Thomas, 1800s, (color engraving) (Folder M1793)
      Included with signed letter written by Alexander Hamilton, signed by George Washington twice and sealed with his signet ring, and sent to Thomas Jefferson. Location: locked Carrell 215.
    - Washington, George, 1800s, (color engraving) (Folder M1794)
  - People Oversize Subseries, 1722-1946 and undated
    - Bodley, Sir Thomas, 1823 Jan. 1 (Ovsz. Folder 44), (engraving) (Box M02)
    - Bonaparte, Napoleon II..., 1828 Jan. 1 (Ovsz. Folder 45), (engraving) (Box M02)
    - Brewer, David J., undated (Ovsz. Folder 46), (card photograph) (Box M02)
    - Brooks, Eugene Clyde, I, 1923 (Ovsz. Folder 47), (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box M02)
      Removed from M616 to the Oversize Series.
    - Brougham, Henry Peter, Baron Brougham and Vaux (1778-1868), undated(Ovsz. Folder 48), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed to the Oversize Subseries from M619.
    - Burkholder, Charles I, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 49), (black-and-white photograph) (Box M02)
    - Byron, George Gordon Noel, Sixth Baron Byron, 1816 Jan. 30 (Ovsz. Folder 50), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed from M645.
    - Caldwell, Joseph Pearson, undated (Ovsz. Folder 51), (sketch) (Box M02)
    - Calhoun, J. C., 1892 (Ovsz. Folder 52), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed from M649.
      Made from a daguerreotype made in 1844.
    - Cannon Mills Plant No.1 -- Kannapolis, NC, 1928 (Ovsz. Folder 53), (black-and-white photograph) (Box M02)
    - Caroline (1683-1737), Queen of Great Britain, undated (Ovsz. Folder 54), (engraving) (Box M02)
    - Carr, Julian Shakespeare (1845-1923), undated (Ovsz. Folder 55), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed from M671.
    - Charles I, King of Great Britain, undated(Ovsz. Folder 56), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed from M691.
    - Charles II, King of Great Britain, undated(Ovsz. Folder 57), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed from M692.
    - Charlotte Augusta, Princess of Wales and Saxe -- Coburg, 1819 Aug. 1 (Ovsz. Folder 58), (engraving) (Box M02)
    - Clay, Henry, 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 59), (lithograph) (Box M02)
    - Clinton, Sir Henry, undated (Ovsz. Folder 60), (engraving) (Box M02)
      Removed from M724.
    - Collins, Wilkie, 1887 Feb. 5 (Ovsz. Folder 61), (engraving) (Box M02)
    - Confederate Generals..., 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 62), (3 engravings and 1 black-and-white photographic illustration) (Box LG02)
      Removed from M745.3.
    - Confederate and Union Commanders, 1884 and 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 63), (2 black-and-white photographic illustrations) (Box LG02)
    - Cowles, Calvin Josiah, 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 64), (engraving) (Box LG02)
    - Craven, William, Earl of Craven, undated (Ovsz. Folder 65), (engraving) (Box M03)
    - Daniels, Josephus, circa 1940s (Ovsz. Folder 66), (2 black-and-white photographs) (Box M03)
      Removed from M788.
    - Davis, Jefferson, 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 67), (2 card photographs) (Box M03)
      Removed from M798.4.
    - Davis, Jefferson, and Clay, Clement Claiborne, 1866 (Ovsz. Folder 68), (card photograph) (Box M03)
    - Davis, John William, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 69), (black-and-white photograph) (Box M03)
      Removed from M802.
    - De Soto, Hernando, undated (Ovsz. Folder 70), (engraving) (Box M03)
    - Doub, Peter, undated (Ovsz. Folder 71), (lithograph) (Box M03)
    - Dundas, Henry, First Viscount Melville, 1831 (Ovsz. Folder 72), (engraving) (Box M03)
    - Dupont, Samuel Francis, 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 73), (engraving) (Box M03)
      Removed from M846.
    - Dyer, George Leland, 1909 Jan. 1 (Ovsz. Folder 74), (card photograph) (Box M03)
    - Early, Jubal Anderson, 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 75), (engraving) (Box M03)
      Signed by Jubal Anderson Early.
      Removed from M850.
    - Edward VI, King of England, 1833 Sept. 1 (Ovsz. Folder 76), (engraving) (Box M03)
    - Einstein, Albert, 1900s (Ovsz. Folder 77), (clipping) (Box LG03)
    - Emerson, Ralph Waldo, 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 78), (black-and-white photograph) (Box M03)
    - Few, William Preston, undated (Ovsz. Folder 79), (black-and-white photograph) (Box M03)
    - Flowers, William Washington, undated (Ovsz. Folder 80), (black-and-white photograph) (Box M03)
    - Founding Fathers, "Laying the Foundation of World Leadership," undated(Ovsz. Folder 81), (color photographic illustration) (Box M04)
    - Frederick II (Frederick the Great), King of Prussia, undated(Ovsz. Folder 82), (color illustration) (Box M04)
    - French noblewomen, [12 portraits of French noblewomen], undated(Ovsz. Folder 83), (engraving) (Box M04)
    - George I, King of Great Britain, 1722 (Ovsz. Folder 84), (black-and-white illustration) (Box LG03)
      Image is a reproduction of a pencil sketch.
    - George II, King of Great Britain, 1700s (Ovsz. Folder 85), (engraving) (Box M04)
    - George III, King of Great Britain 1800s (Ovsz. Folder 86), (2 engravings and 1 black-and-white illustration) (Box M04)
    - Goldsborough, William W., undated (Ovsz. Folder 87), (lithograph) (Box M04)